

Contact: +91-9963858538

Abhijeth Dugginapeddi

Security Consultant, Bangalore, Karnataka, India.

Email:abhijeth0423@gmail.com,dabhijeth@yahoo.co.in

Summary:

Experienced in the field of Information Security since past 4 years and currently working as a Security Analyst in Adobe Systems. Has expertise in various domains like Application Security, Network Penetration Testing, Mobile Assessments, and Infrastructure Security etc.

Educational Qualifications:

- > B.E/B.Tech in Information Technology with CGPA 8.28 from GITAM University in 2012, Visakhapatnam.
- > Senior Secondary with 87.6% from Sri Chaitanya IIT Academy in 2008, Hyderabad.
- Secondary S.S.C with 87.8% from Dilsuknagar Public School in 2006, Hyderabad.

Work Experience:

Company: Adobe July 2014-Present

Role: Security Analyst Responsibilities:

- Performing Penetration testing, analyzing vulnerabilities, identifying threats, and recommending counter measures to all the public facing applications
- Code and design reviews for the various products to provide solutions at the architecture level
- Coordinate with the incident response team and handle reports sent through the responsible disclosure program of Adobe.
- Validate and verify different vulnerabilities reported by various researchers around the globe to the organization.
- Training various Engineers in Application Security Threats and Secure coding practices.

Company: Tata Consultancy Services

June 2012 - June 2014

Role: Security Consultant

Responsibilities:

- Coordinated with clients to identify suitable security assessment required for their web applications.
- Performed vulnerability assessments and penetration testing for various devices.
- Experienced in assessment of thick client applications and threat modeling.
- Reviewed security standards of a service provided by a vendor, identified vulnerabilities in the service, categorized findings based on the risk involved and provided recommendations.
- As SME, evaluated security standards of new solutions and technologies to provide more offerings in the practice.

Experience as a student:

Company: SourceNXT Sept 2011 – June 2012

Role: Security Analyst and Technical Head

Responsibilities:

- Co-founded the company with an aim of creating awareness among various organizations
- Conducted training sessions in the field of Information Security.
- Did Security Consulting for 13 clients who were mostly based from US, UK and South Asian countries.
- SourceNXT was later one among the top 10 startups of Hyderabad in the year 2012.

Company: Kyrion Digital Securities

May 2011 - Aug 2011

Role: Security Researcher and Trainer (Intern)

Responsibilities:

- Research on basics of Network Architecture, Network Devices, Network Attacks, OSI, Wireless Networks, Network Security Firewall Implementation, Intrusion Detection Systems, Honeypots and Vulnerability Assessment.
- Trained engineers for certification in the field of Information Security.

Company: Eastern Naval Command

Jan 2011 - Feb 2011

Role: Security Consultant (Intern)

Responsibilities:

- Reported various vulnerabilities, developed a secured website and hosted on their network.
- Performed network security audits and also worked with their wireless security devices.
- Trained on various Information Security techniques to lieutenants of Indian Navy.

Achievements and Honors:

- In the field of Information security since 14 and since then found vulnerabilities in more than 1500 websites
- Being awarded, acknowledged in Hall of Fames for Security Research and Responsible Disclosures by various bug bounty programs.

Critical Vulnerabilities reported: Remote Code Execution, SQLi, XSS, and CSRF in the following

Yahoo -- Top bug reporter for two consecutive months for submitting RCE, XSS, CSRF, CJ

Google – Submitted Authentication Bypass, CSRF, XSS and got acknowledged 5 times.

Facebook – Submitted XSS, logical flaw in facebook.com

Ebay & Paypal – Submitted XSS, CSRF and CJ in subsidiary website

Microsoft – Submitted critical CSRF, XSS in main domains.

Adobe – Submitted critical RCE, CSRF in one of the subdomains

Telekom - Submitted 17 XSS, RCE, DT in mail website AT&T

- Submitted XSS, SQLi in internal websites

HDFC & ICICI Bank - SQLi, XSS, CSRF in main domains

Juniper Networks – Several XSS were submitted

- Trained more than 10,000 students in the field of Information Security and Ethical Hacking
- Currently one Among Top 10 Security Researchers among the world in Synack- a crowd sourcing security platform
- Recognized as youngest ever freelance security consultant to work for Naval base, Visakhapatnam.
- Delivered talks as a speaker at top universities like IITK, ISM Dhanbad, AU, JNTU, GITAM, CBIT etc
- Presented at Null Hyderabad Chapter an open source security platform on Honeypots.
- Worked on few forensic investigations for intelligence departments.
- Worked as Joint secretary for "CSI Computer Society of India", GITAM University.
- Co-Founder and advisory member of "GUSAC GITAM University Science and Activity Centre", largest student activity center started by students.
- Also recognized for being young student entrepreneur in various newspapers and at various events.
- Mentoring various startups in Hyderabad on various platforms.
- Received more than 15 awards for various presentations across the country.

PROJECTS

VAPT on Network Devices and Web Applications

Client: UK based Insurance Company

Performed VAPT on 31 web applications and 317 devices

Tools used: HPWebinspect, Nessus, Nmap, BurpSuite free, SQLmap, Metasploit, Backtrack

Web Application Framework Testing

Client: Largest Pharmaceutical chain in US

Tested around 130 applications and also Report Analysis

Tools used: BurpSuite Professional, SQLmap, Qualysguard VM tool, IronWASP

Web Application Penetration Testing

Analyzed around 67 Web applications

Client: UK based Telecom Service Provider

Tools used:

HPWebinspect, Metasploit, Burp Suite, SQLmap, Paros, Knock

Network Analysis and Web exploitation

Client: Small scale organization

Worked with IDS and also with Qualys

Tools used: Snort, Wireshark, QualysGuard, Metasploit

Web Application Penetration Testing

Client: Leading E commerce application

Analyzed a large E commerce application

Tools used: Acunetix Web vulnerability Scanner, Metasploit, BurpSuite, SQLmap, Zap Proxy

· Freelance web VAPT

Clients: Various website owners

Helped in finding and fixing vulnerabilities

Tools used: BurpSuite, SQLmap, Paros, OWASP CSRF tester, Xenotix framework, DOMinatorpro.

Interests:

Application Security, Bug Hunting, Network Penetration Testing, Digital Marketing, Social Media Marketing, Presales.